{
    "id": "d6d36105a25a4d0f9c88357d4d2c52ab",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise (Beginner)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c904dd042da143398668994ca8436e31",
            "title": "General Grammar Exercise (Beginner)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We ............................... heard anything from them yet.",
                    "description": "We use have before the third form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "aren't",
                        "didn't",
                        "haven't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. you think we are doing the right thing?",
                    "description": "We use do with you.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... you see him yesterday?",
                    "description": "We use the simple past with past time expressions like yesterday. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Have",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... you free this evening?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Are",
                        "Do",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long ....................................... it take you to finish a project?",
                    "description": "Does is used with the first form of the verb has is used with the third form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ...................................... rung back yet.",
                    "description": "We use has/have/had with the third form of the verb. The past perfect is totally unnecessary here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't",
                        "hadn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... you call her in the morning?",
                    "description": "We use did in the simple past. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Have",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ you play football when you were young?",
                    "description": "Did is used with the first form of the verb. Have and had are used with the third form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Have",
                        "Had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ you enjoy your stay here?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Have",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... you enjoying this visit?",
                    "description": "With ing forms we use are/is/am/was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Are",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. anybody here?",
                    "description": "Anybody is used with a singular verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Is",
                        "Are",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where ........................................ they live?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}